[
    {
        "prompt": "Who Is The Developer Of Ruby?",
       "options": [ "Yukihiro Matsumoto", "Bill Gates", "Brendan Eich", "Satoshi Nakamoto", "Life Line" ],
       "answer": "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
       "lifeline": "Life Line",
       "value": "$500"
    },

    {
        "prompt": "Which Array Method Will Remove Nil Values In Ruby?",
        "options": [ "compact", "flatten", "filter",  "map", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "compact",
        "lifeline": "Life Line",
        "value": "$1,000"
    },

    {
        "prompt": "Which Of The Following Is Not An Object In Ruby?",
        "options": [ "method", "string", "array", "hash", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "method",
        "lifeline": "Life Line",
        "value": "$2,000"
    },

    {
        "prompt": "How Many Types Of Variables Are Used In Ruby?",
        "options": [ "6", "2", "4", "8", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "4",
        "lifeline": "Life Line",
        "value": "$5,000"
    },

    {
       "prompt": "Ruby Is What Type Of Programming Language?",
       "options": [ "Strongly Typed / Statically Type", "Strongly Typed / Dynamically Typed", "Weakly Typed / Statically Typed", "Weakly Typed / Dynamically Typed", "Life Line"],
       "answer": "Strongly Typed / Dynamically Typed",
       "value": "$10,000" 
    },

    {
        "prompt": "What Is The Value Of The Variable Upcased In The Piece Of Code Below \n upcased = ['one', 'two', 'three'].map {|n| puts n.upcase}",
        "options": [ "upcased = ['ONE', 'TWO', 'THREE']", "upcased = ['One', 'Two', 'Three']", "upcased = [nil, nil, nil]", "upcased = ['one', 'two', 'three']", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "upcased = [nil, nil, nil]",
        "value": "$20,000"
    },

    {
        "prompt": "Identify The Objects In The Following Line Of Code random_stuff = [:tall, 'dude', 45.23]?",
        "options": [":tall", "dude", "45.23", "all of the above", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "value": "$50,000"
    },

    {
       "prompt": "What Does a||=b Evaluate To, When a = nil and b = 2?",
       "options": ["a = a,  b = a", "a = b, b = b", "a = a, b = b", "TypeError"],
       "answer": "a = b, b = b",
       "lifeline": "Life Line",
       "value": "$75,000"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Which of the following is supported by Ruby?",
        "options": ["Dynamic Type System", "Multiple Programming Paradigms", "Autmatic Memory Management", "All Of The Above", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "All Of The Above",
        "lifeline": "Life Line",
        "value": "$150,000"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Variables That Start With A Dollar Sign Are What Kind Of Variables In Ruby?",
        "options": ["Local variable", "Global variable", "Instance variable", "Class variable", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "Global variable",
        "lifeline": "Life Line",
        "value": "$250,000"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "What Does %x!ls! Represent?",
        "options": ["Same as back tick command output `ls`", "Same as 'x'", "Same as 'xls'", "None of the above", "Life Line"],
        "answer": "Same as back tick command output `ls`",
        "lifeline": "Life Line",
        "value": "$500,000"
    }

]
